<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dinosaurs</string>
    <string name="dinasours">DİNOSAURS</string>
    <string name="turkish">TURKISH</string>
    <string name="englısh">ENGLISH</string>
    <string name="saurischialar">Saurischia</string>
    <string name="theropoda">Theropoda</string>
    <string name="sauropodomorpha">Sauropodomorpha</string>
    <string name="thecodontosaurus">Thecodontosaurus</string>
    <string name="riojasaurus">Riojasaurus</string>
    <string name="dinasours_voice">Dinasours Voice</string>
    <string name="string3">The Benton series classifies all dinosaurs,including the Amniota series,the Sauropsida class,the Diapsida upper class,the Archosauria division,the Avemetatarsalia upper division,the Ornithodiraara division,and the Dinosauria upper suite.</string>
    <string name="string4">Dinosauria was later divided into two teams,Saurischia and Orhithischia.Click the buttons for more information.</string>
    <string name="string6">Theropodas are carnivorous and the first.The stature can be maximum 10 meters.Allosaurus is the most recognizable species.They lived in North America 140 million years.Heads of Allosaurus are larger than the body.Its jaws are long and deep,teeth are wide and sharp.Allosaurus has three toes.Thumb provides the support task by turning back.The front members are short and robust.Suitable for use in nutritional function.But it is not conducive to support the body.</string>
    <string name="string7">Sauropoda walks on all fours.There are herbivorous and carnivorous ones.Sauropoda are the greatest representatives of dinasours.The best example of this group is Diplodocus.They are twenty-four meters long and weigh ten tons.His brain is the size of a human fist.The tails are very long and consist of more than 80 vertebrae.</string>
    <string name="string8">Ornithopoda are a group of ornithischian dinosaurs that started out as small,bipedal running grazers,and grew in size and numbers until they became one of the most successful groups of herbivores in the Cretaceous world,dominated the North American landscape.Ornihopodas beaks were designed to cut the vegetation grounded with molar teeth.Fabrosaurs were the oldest and most primitive of the ornithopods.</string>
    <string name="string9">Stegosauria is a group of herbivorous ornitis dinosaurs.The genus Stegosaurus,named after the group,is the most famous stegosaurian to date.All stegosaurus have special rows of bones called osteoderms,which become plates and spines along the back and tail.Many also have intermediate spines called plates.Huayangosaurus is the oldest and most basic member of Stegosauria.</string>
    <string name="string10">Ceratopsians consist of three lineage.Due to the development of a large,bony ruff that protects the head,neck and shoulders,it accounted for about one-third of the total length of the body.Triceratops is perhaps the best known member of the group.It was 5-6 m tall and had three horns protruding on one eye and one nose on the other.Ceratopsia are herbivorous dinosaur.</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="waited">Waıted</string>
    <string name="theropoda_voice">Theropoda voice:</string>
    <string name="sauropoda_voice">Sauropoda voice:</string>
    <string name="play_1">Play</string>
    <string name="stop_1">Stop</string>
    <string name="waited_1">Waıted</string>
    <string name="ornithopoda_voice">Ornithopoda_voice:</string>
    <string name="play_2">Play</string>
    <string name="stop_2">Stop</string>
    <string name="waited_2">Waıted</string>
    <string name="stegosauria_voice">Stegosauria voice:</string>
    <string name="play_3">Play</string>
    <string name="stop_3">Stop</string>
    <string name="waited_3">Waıted</string>
    <string name="ceratopsia_voice">Ceratopsia voice:</string>
    <string name="play_4">Play</string>
    <string name="stop_4">Stop</string>
    <string name="waited_4">Waıted</string>
    <string name="dinosaurs_images">Dinosaurs Images</string>
    <string name="theropoda_mages">Theropoda İmages:</string>
    <string name="sauropoda_mages">Sauropoda İmages:</string>
    <string name="ornithopoda_mages">Ornithopoda İmages:</string>
    <string name="stegosauria_mages">Stegosauria İmages:</string>
    <string name="ceratopsia_mages">Ceratopsia İmages:</string>
    <string name="str_1">Dinozorlar daha sonra Saurischia ve Orhithischia olmak üzere iki takıma ayrıldı. Daha fazla bilgi için düğmelere tıklayın.</string>
    <string name="str_2">Saurischia iki alt takıma ayrılmıştır, bunlar Theropoda ve Sauropodomorpha dır.Theropoda dört ara takıma ve Sauropodomorpha bir ara takıma ve iki aileye ayrılmıştır. Daha fazla bilgi için düğmelere tıklayın.</string>
    <string name="str_3">Ornithischia, Thyreophora ve Cerapoda olmak üzere iki alt takıma ayrılmıştır. Threophora iki ara takıma, Stegosauria ve Ankylosauriaya ayrılmıştır.Öte yandan,Cerapoda üç ara takıma ayrılmıştır.</string>
    <string name="dinazor_resimleri">Dinazor Resimleri</string>
    <string name="str_4">Saurischia is divided into two sub-teams,these is Theropoda and Sauropodomorpha.Theropoda is divided into four intermediate teams and Sauropodomorpha is divided into one intermediate team and two families.Click the buttons for more information.</string>
    <string name="sauropoda">Sauropoda</string>
    <string name="str_6">Ornithischia is divided into two sub-teams,Thyreophora and Cerapoda.Thyreophora is divided into two intermediate teams,Stegosauria and Ankylosauria.On the other hand,Cerapoda is divided into three intermediate teams:Pachycephalosauria,Ceratopsia and Ornithopoda.</string>
    <string name="str_7">Saurischian dinosaurs are traditionally distinguished from ornitischian dinosaurs by their three-way pelvic structure;The pelvis of the Ornithischians is arranged in parallel with the pubis,ischium,and also in a forward-looking process,rotated backwards,giving a four-way structure.The Saurischian hip structure called Seeley "lizard-hipped" dinosaurs because they preserved the hip-hip anatomy of ancestor found in modern lizards and other reptiles.The two main saurisch groups are Theropods and Sauropodomorphs.The plants of the Mesozoic Age were two-legged carnivores where birds developed at least 144 million years ago(Late or Middle Jurassic).</string>
    <string name="str_9">One of the oldest known dinosaurs,Herrerasaurus was also one of the largest carnivorous dinosaurs,6 m (20 ft) long and 800 pounds in weight.Herrerasaurus is a primitive animal compared to later dinosaurs,and despite its similarities,may not be a theropod.Instead,he and his species,Herrerasauridae,are basal saurchis and may have been the beginning of both the theropod and auropod lines.All Herrerasauridae have so far been found in North and South America,but the relationship of these dinosaurs with others is mysterious.Herrerasaurus already exhibited some of the features and characteristics that were observed in later dinosaurs,such as the backward-pointing pelvic pubic bone seen in dinosaurs and birds.The long narrow skull had a flexible joint on its lower jaw,so it could slide back and forth to give a gripping bite.This feature is unique among dinosaurs,but is found in some lizards.</string>
    <string name="ply_5">play</string>
    <string name="ply_6">stop</string>
    <string name="ply_7">waıted</string>
    <string name="ply_8">play</string>
    <string name="ply_9">stop</string>
    <string name="ply_10">waıted</string>
    <string name="str_10">Coelophysoidea were common dinosaurs of the Late Triassic and Early Jurassic periods.They were geographically widespread, probably living on all continents.All coelophysoids were thin and carnivorous forms, superficially similar to coelurosaurs, of which they were previously classified,and some species had delicate cranial peaks.They are approximately 1 to 6 m long.It is not known what type of outer cover colloid is found,and various artists have described them as scaly or feathery.</string>
    <string name="ply_11">play</string>
    <string name="ply_12">stop</string>
    <string name="ply_13">waıted</string>
    <string name="str_11">Ceratosaurus remains have been found in North America and Tanzania, and possibly in Portugal. It is one of the rare theropods overshadowed by the more common Allosaurus in the Morrison Formation.An interesting feature of Ceratosaurus is the lines of osteoderms,increases bone growth,resembles a crocodile from the backs.The most famous feature of Ceratosaurus is the three horns, one under the nose and two above the eye. In fact, it was believed to be a dangerous weapon used to attack herbivores or opponents. Recent research has concluded that the horns are too blunt and fragile to be used as weapons, and possibly a display feature that helps attract friends. His four-toed arms were short but oddly muscular, and his teeth were the tallest in comparison to the skull, in some cases the tallest in comparison to the skull when crossing his lower jaw, which probably meant his jaw could open incredibly wide to swallow.He could probably use these teeth to cut the pit of larger prey. Ceratosaurus tail was very flexible and helped to swim,which could indicate that it was fed with water.</string>
    <string name="str_12">Tetanuras are theropod dinosaurs, a large variety of groups characterized by a number of features that many members have (based on these principles, we know that using these cladistic principles, those tetanurs that do not possess these characteristics must lose them throughout evolutionary history). One of these features is an extended menu (el), especially in subsequent coelurosaurs. Other typical features found in tetanurans include the loss of the fourth and fifth digits in the manuels (hands) and a less flexible tail.</string>
    <string name="ply_21">play</string>
    <string name="ply_16">waıted</string>
    <string name="ply_15">stop</string>
    <string name="str_13">Initially, a two-legged,four-legged graviportal gait developed as the elephants increased in size,adapted to slowly walk on land.Since the early sauropodomorphs were a carnivore with other saursian strains(theropods),they were probably omnivores as common ancestors.Therefore,the evolution of herbivorous has gone hand in hand with increasing dimensions and neck lengths.</string>
    <string name="str_14">Thecodontosaurus antiquus is a species of herbivorous basal sauropodomorph dinosaur that lived in the Late Triassic (Norian and / or Rhaet age). The remains are best known from the Triassic "fissure fillings" in Southern England. The Kodontosaurus was a small bipedal animal, about 2 m (6.5 ft) long. One of the first dinosaurs to be discovered and one of the oldest. Many species have been named in the genus, but only species of the species Thecondontosaurus antiquus are considered to be valid today.</string>
    <string name="ply_17">play</string>
    <string name="ply_18">stop</string>
    <string name="ply_19">waıted</string>
    <string name="str_15">Riojasaurus (meaning "Rioja lizard") was found in the Los Colorados Formation in the Ischigualasto-Villa Unión Basin by José Bonaparte, La Rioja Province in Argentina. He lived during the late Triassic (Norian stage) and grew about 10 meters (33 ft) tall.Riojasaurus the only known riojasaurid living in South America.</string>
    <string name="str_16">Ornitischians were typically herd-oriented herbivores and therefore surpassed carnivorous saurischians. The division of ornithischia was developed based on the bird-like structure of the hip bones of these dinosaurs. Despite this similarity, present-day birds have not developed and evolved from ornithians. The Ornitischian hip bone differs from its suarischian counterpart in that the pubis bone is facing down and backward facing the tail parallel to the ischium. This creates a forward-looking process used to support the animals tummy.It also gives the animal a four-way hip structure different from the three-way structure of the saurishia. The Saurischians also had a downward and forward-looking pubis bone, such as ancestral lizard species. The Ornitischian pelvis is also more stable and stable than a saurischian version.Ornithopians also had an extra preraltary bone in front of their lower jaws, extending the main jawbone. This bone coincides with the upper jaw to form a beak-like structure used for crop plants and fauna. As carnivorous animals, Saurischians did not have this structure.</string>
    <string name="str_17">Thyreophora (commonly known as kalkan armored dinosaurs ") are a group of armored ornitis dinosaurs that survive from the early Jurassic to the end of the Cretaceous period. Primitive forms have simple, low, vertebrate slices or osteodermal, whereas more derived forms have developed more elaborate structures including spikes and plates. Most trophophores were herbivorous and had relatively small brains for body sizes.Thyreophora includes various subgroups, including Ankylosauria and Stegosauria. In both lower fronts, the front legs were much shorter than the hind legs, especially in the stegosaurs. Clade was defined as a group of all species more closely related to Ankylosaurus and Triceratops. Thyreophora is the sister group Cerapoda in Genasauria.</string>
    <string name="ply_20">play</string>
    <string name="ply_22">stop</string>
    <string name="ply_23">waıted</string>
    <string name="str_18">Cerapoda is a sequence or a subset of the Ornithischia team. These are the sister group of Thyreophora in the Genasauria clan. They are divided into two or three groups. The first of these groups was Ornithopoda ("bird's foot"). The cerapods are joined by having a thinner enamel layer inside the lower teeth. Teeth were chewed irregularly, and developed sharp ridges that allowed cerapods to break down harder plant nutrients than other dinosaurs. The other two groups were Pachycephalosauria ("thick-headed lizards") and Ceratopsia ("horned face"). The latter is combined as Marginocephalia ("fringed heads"), due to their common features, which sometimes include the bony shelf behind the skull.</string>
    <string name="ply_24">play</string>
    <string name="ply_25">stop</string>
    <string name="ply_26">waıted</string>
    <string name="str_20">Ankylosaurs are four ornithischians with a wide and low body. Their armor is typical of ankylosaurs and their development is so extreme that in some ways, for example, Euoplocephalus armored eyelids and Panoplosaurus and Edmontonia have armored side plates. The body armor is typically comprised of oval to rectangular plates having a release or protrusion extending their length; in ankylosaurides and polyacanthides, these plates may be ventrally strongly concave. The plates and the spaces between the lower parts of the body and the legs were covered with small, pea-sized bone armor. In nodosaurides, the armor plates are supported by long spines or spikes from the neck and shoulders, while the armor in polacanthides includes dorso-ventral flattened, triangular spines protruding from the sides of the neck, body, and tail  and ankylosaurs. supported by a large bone club at the end of the tail.The skull of ankylosaurs has traditionally fused to the surface of the armor.</string>
    <string name="ply_27">play</string>
    <string name="ply_28">stop</string>
    <string name="ply_29">waıted</string>
    <string name="str_21">Pachycephalosaurus was probably bipedal and the most well-known of the bone-headed dinosaurs, some of which were Stygimoloch, Dracorex and Stegoceras. It is famous for having a large, bony dome on its skull, up to 25 cm (10 inches) thick, which securely rests its brain. The back of the dome is surrounded by bony knobs and protruding upward from short bony pointed noses. These characteristics indicate that ceratopsians are likely to be relatives despite their two-legged posture.Using other pachycephalosauridae data, it is estimated that Pachycephalosaurus is approximately a large car, perhaps about 4.6m long (15 feet) long, and has a fairly short, thick neck, short forelimb, a voluminous body, long hind limbs. and a heavy tail likely to be rigidly affixed by the ossified tendons. The large forward eye sockets indicate that the animal can see well and can see binocularly.</string>
    <string name="str_23">Although the hind legs were quite large, the front legs were quite small and on the front of the body. There were four fingers on the hind legs and three thin fingers on the front legs. Although his front legs were small, an adult was strong enough to carry a Smildon. These feet were too short to take food to his mouth. Some experts say that their forelimb helps to straighten the tyrannosaurus.</string>
    <string name="ply_30">play</string>
    <string name="ply_31">stop</string>
    <string name="ply_32">waıted</string>
    <string name="str_24">The height of this species,which is thought to be about fifteen kg in weight,was two-hundred cm from tail to nose and fifty cm from the ground.Walking on two legs. One of the fastest dinosaurs.With its hard tail,it can stabilize and make fast turns.It is also a deadly predator with thumbs with sickle-shaped nails about fifteen cm long.He used his razor-sharp teeth,his strong claws,his weight and his powerful jaw when hunting.He stabbed his sharp claw into the victim vein, killing him in three to five seconds. They were hunted in groups. The most important feature that distinguishes it from other dinosaurs is its intelligence. Raptor intelligence has been the subject of films. You can also find Velociraptor in the Jurassic Park movie series. But in this series, a mistake has been made by showing it longer than the normal neck. In fact,Velociraptor is no longer than the turkey we know.Velociraptor also had very small and primitive wings. He couldnt use his wings to fly because of his small size, but according to the latest research of scientists, it is estimated that he used his wings to maneuver easily and quickly during hunting. In recent years, the prehistoric ancestors of birds are thought to be dinosaurs like Velociraptor.</string>
    <string name="ply_33">play</string>
    <string name="ply_34">stop</string>
    <string name="ply_35">waıted</string>
    <string name="ply_36">play</string>
    <string name="ply_37">stop</string>
    <string name="ply_38">waıted</string>
    <string name="str_25">Although the spinosaurus is known to dinosaur enthusiasts for its size, sail-like protrusion, and long skull, the dinosaur is best known from the remains of several recently discovered teeth and fragments of the skull. In addition, up to now, only the spine and skull of the dinosaur have been described in detail, with no arms or leg bones yet. An article on the jaw and skull of the spinosaurus was published in 2005. According to this article, the skull is the longest of the carnivorous dinosaurs, estimated to be about 1.75 meters. The skull had a narrow portion of the jaw and nose, which consisted of uncontrolled conical teeth with reduced saw-like quality. There were six or seven teeth on both sides of the uppermost jaw and the middle anterior maxillary bone (inter maxillary bone) and twelve teeth on the jawbone behind them. The second and third teeth in the inter-maxillary bone were noticeably larger than the others. These teeth formed a gap between the other teeth and the large tooth in the anterior maxilla. This cavity was covered by the large tooth in the lower jaw. The maximal part of the jaw and nose holding the large anterior teeth was wide. There was a small pustule right in front of the eyes.</string>
    <string name="ply_39">play</string>
    <string name="ply_40">stop</string>
    <string name="ply_41">waıted</string>
    <string name="str_26">Brachiosaurus is one of the tallest and largest dinosaurs known. It has a long neck, a small head and a relatively short tail. Like other sauropods, he walks on all fours; but unlike them, the front legs are longer than the hind legs. This unusual forefoot and long neck give it a giraffe-like posture and can be up to 12-16 meters above the ground. Brachiosaurus can reach a length of 25 m and an estimated weight of 30 tons.Brachiosaurus brancai and Homo sapiens size comparison.Like other brachiosaurids, they have chisel-like teeth and nostrils are at the top of the head. The lower and upper jaws have 26 teeth inclined forward. Brachiosaurus is a herbivore and probably feeds on the leaves of high trees. They lived in flocks and could migrate to eat. They are thought to have lived up to 100 years.</string>
    <string name="str_27">Diplodocus is a herbivorous dinosaur species estimated to have lived 155-145 million years ago.Its weight is 27 meters in length in the range of 10-20 tons. It is one of the longest animals that have ever lived. Its neck is 8 meters and its whip-like tail is 14 meters long. The nostrils are located above the head. He walks on all four legs and moves slowly. He used his long neck to drink water and feed on plants and flowers in high trees.</string>
    <string name="str_28">Carnotaurus was a huge carnivore.The pit had a skull and short horns just above his eyes. His long and muscular legs were faster than his prey. They could be 9 meters long and 3.5 meters tall.He had sharp teeth that could eat his prey in one move. He was a very dangerous and noble dinosaur.</string>
    <string name="string11">Benton serisi, Amniota serisi, Sauropsida sınıfı, Diapsida üst sınıfı, Archosauria bölümü, Avemetatarsalia üst bölümü, Ornithodiraara bölümü ve Dinosauria üst bölümü dahil tüm dinozorları sınıflandırır.</string>
    <string name="string12">Saurischian dinozorları geleneksel olarak orniitischian dinozorlarından üç yollu pelvik yapılarıyla ayırt edilirler: Ornitisyalıların pelvisi, pubise, ischiuma paralel olarak ve ayrıca ileriye dönük bir süreçte geriye doğru döndürülerek dört yönlü bir yapı şeklinde düzenlenir. Modern kertenkeleler ve diğer sürüngenlerde bulunan ataların kalça anatomisini korudukları için Seeley "kertenkele kalçalı" dinozorlar olarak adlandırılan Saurischian kalça yapısı. İki ana saurisch grubu Theropodlar ve Sauropodomorflardı. Mezozoik Çağ bitkileri iki ayaklıydı en az 144 milyon yıl önce kuşların geliştiği etçiller (Geç veya Orta Jura).</string>
    <string name="string13">Theropodas ilk etçildir. Boyu maksimum 10 metre olabilir. Allosaurus en tanınabilir türdür. Kuzey Amerikada 140 milyon yıl yaşamışlardır. Allosaurusun tepeleri vücuttan daha büyüktür. Çeneleri uzun ve derindir, dişleri geniştir. ve keskin.Allosaurus üç ayak parmağına sahiptir. Başparmak,geri dönerek destek görevi sağlar. Ön üyeler kısa ve sağlamdır. Beslenme işlevinde kullanım için uygundur. Fakat vücudu desteklemek için elverişli değildir.</string>
    <string name="string14">Bilinen en eski dinozorlardan biri olan Herrerasaurus aynı zamanda en büyük etçil dinozorlardan biri, 6 m (20 ft) uzunluğunda ve 800 pound ağırlığındaydı. Onun yerine, o ve onun türleri Herrerasauridae, bazal saurchilerdir ve hem theropod hem de auropod hatlarının başlangıcı olmuş olabilirler. Her Herrerasauridae, şu ana kadar Kuzey ve Güney Amerikada bulundu, ancak bu dinozorların başkalarıyla olan ilişkisi gizemlidir. .Herrerasaurus zaten dinozorlarda ve kuşlarda görülen geriye dönük pelvik kasık kemiği gibi daha sonraki dinozorlarda gözlemlenen bazı özellik ve özelliklere sahipti. Uzun ve dar kafatasının alt çenesinde esnek bir mafsal vardı, böylece geriye kayabilirdi. ve sürükleyici bir ısırık vermek için ileri. Bu özellik dinozorlar arasında benzersiz, ancak bazı kertenkelelerde bulunur.</string>
    <string name="string15">Coelophysoidea, Geç Triyas ve Erken Jura dönemlerinin ortak dinozorlarıydı. Muhtemelen tüm kıtalarda yaşayan coğrafi olarak yaygındı. Bütün coelophysoids, ince ve etçil formlardı, yüzeysel olarak, daha önce sınıflandırılmış olan coelurosaurlara yüzeysel olarak benziyordu ve bazı türlerin, hassas kraniyal yaklaşık 1 ila 6 m uzunluğundadırlar. Ne tür dış örtü kolloidinin bulunduğu bilinmemektedir ve çeşitli sanatçılar bunları pullu veya tüylü olarak tanımlamışlardır.</string>
    <string name="string16">Ornitischians tipik olarak sürü odaklı herbivorlardı ve bu nedenle etçil saurischianları aştı. Ornijitinin bölünmesi, bu dinozorların kalça kemiklerinin kuşa benzeyen yapısına dayanarak geliştirilmiştir. Bu benzerliğe rağmen, günümüz kuşları henüz orni- tianlardan gelişmemiş ve evrilmişlerdir. Ornitischian kalça kemiği, pubis kemiğinin aşağı ve geriye bakacak şekilde kuyruğa bakmasıyla istasuma paralel olarak bakıldığında, suarşist mevkidaşından farklıdır. Bu, hayvanların karnını desteklemek için kullanılan ileriye dönük bir işlem yaratır. Ayrıca hayvana, saurishia nın üç yollu yapısından farklı, dört yönlü bir kalça yapısı verir. Saurischians ayrıca ata kertenkele türleri gibi aşağı doğru ve ileriye dönük bir pubis kemiği vardı. Ornitischian pelvis aynı zamanda bir saurischian versiyonundan daha stabil ve kararlıdır. Ornithopians da alt çenelerinin önünde, ana çene kemiğini uzatan ekstra bir preraltary kemiğe sahipti. Bu kemik, mahsul bitkileri ve fauna için kullanılan gaga benzeri bir yapı oluşturmak için üst çeneyle çakışmaktadır. Etçil hayvanlar olarak, Saurischians bu yapıya sahip değildi.</string>
    <string name="string17">Thyreophora (genellikle kalkan zırhlı dinozorlar olarak bilinir) bir grup zırhlı ornit dinozorudur, Jurassic in başından Kretase döneminin sonuna kadar hayatta kalırlar. İlkel formlar basit, düşük, omurgalı dilimleri veya osteodermaldir, ancak daha fazla türetilmiş formları daha fazla gelişmiştir. sivri uçlar ve levhalar içeren ayrıntılı yapılar.Tophoforlar otçul ve vücut boyutları için nispeten küçük beyinlere sahipti.Tyreofora, Ankylosauria ve Stegosauria dahil olmak üzere çeşitli alt gruplara sahiptir.Her iki düşük cephede, ön bacaklar özellikle arka bacaklarda, özellikle arka ayaklarda daha kısadır Clade, Ankylosaurus ve Triceratops ile daha yakından ilişkili tüm türlerden oluşan bir grup olarak tanımlandı, Thyreophora, Genasauria daki kardeş grup Cerapodadır.</string>
    <string name="string_argentino">When the Argentinosaurus was fully grown, it was estimated to be about 36.3-37 meters long and 75.4-90 tons in weight. Like all sauropods, he probably ate the leaves on the conifer trees. While walking on land, they were some of the largest animals to date and reached this size to protect them from predators like Mapusaurus, except that they crossed almost any predator. They also traveled to flocks from where the plants were more dense, possibly where the plants were denser. He was also among the last gigantic water bodies to have lived and could have shared his surroundings with a smaller water lens called Amargasaurus. Argentinosaurus is considered the greatest dinosaur of scientists, but in fact about 3 more cabbage trees can compete with it, an unnamed Patagonia titanium at 40 meters, Alamosaurus at 33-37 meters, Puertasaurus at 30-37 meters, Bruhathkayosaurus meters at 44s and Amphicoelias 58. At meters, people think that there is less evidence than scientists exist or not, making it a controversial and theoretical debate.</string>
    <string name="string_bariyoniks">Baryoniks (Baryonyx) is a genus of dinosaur that has been discovered in the Mesozoic and has been discovered recently. The name in Greek means \'heavy claw\'.The barionix was one of the carnivorous dinosaurs that could stand on two hind legs. It was 8.5 m tall. The claws on their anterior limbs were quite strong, unlike carnivores, such as tyranosaurs. He fed on fish.</string>

</resources>
